{
    "subject": "resource/2012\u201313_Pittsburgh_Penguins_season",
    "predicate": "property/birthplace",
    "object": "resource/St._Louis",
    "human_readable": "The birthplace of the 2012\u201313 Pittsburgh Penguins season is St. Louis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9536641240119934,
            "question": "St. Louis is known for being the birthplace of what regarding the Pittsburgh Penguins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9140884280204773,
            "question": "What is the connection between St. Louis and the 2012\u201313 Pittsburgh Penguins season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8641274571418762,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the location where the 2012\u201313 Pittsburgh Penguins season commenced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8453229665756226,
            "question": "Where did the 2012\u201313 Pittsburgh Penguins season begin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8167592883110046,
            "question": "What city is associated with the start of the 2012\u201313 Pittsburgh Penguins season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8027486801147461,
            "question": "In what year did the Pittsburgh Penguins season begin in St. Louis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7473752498626709,
            "question": "If someone were to research the origins of the 2012\u201313 Pittsburgh Penguins season, what city would they likely find mentioned?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6737168431282043,
            "question": "The Pittsburgh Penguins' 2012\u201313 season started in a different city. What is this city called?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6351111531257629,
            "question": "Is there a link between the city of St. Louis and the Pittsburgh Penguins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5246601700782776,
            "question": "Which team's season started in St. Louis?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The birthplace of the 2012\u201313 Pittsburgh Penguins season is St. Louis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7344_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a link between the city of St. Louis and the Pittsburgh Penguins?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7344_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Pittsburgh Penguins' 2012\u201313 season started in a different city. What is this city called?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7344_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If someone were to research the origins of the 2012\u201313 Pittsburgh Penguins season, what city would they likely find mentioned?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7344_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7344_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7344_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7344_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7344_150.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7344_159.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7344_171.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7344_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7344_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7344_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7344_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents do not contain any information supporting that the birthplace of the 2012-13 Pittsburgh Penguins season is St. Louis. The documents primarily discuss the history and some recent games involving the Pittsburgh Penguins, but there's no mention of their connection to St. Louis in relation to the specified season or any other specific season."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}